<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Lab_2.1</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="house_of_the_dragons">House of The Dragon</string>
    <string name="about_page_info">This app is about House of the dragons series, and it includes a random House of the dragon generator and some pictures and fan art Enjoy..!</string>
    <string name="if_daenerys_had_three_dragons_in_game_of_thrones_the_number_of_creatures_present_in_house_of_the_dragon_is_going_to_be_huge_ryan_j_condal_the_tv_show_co_creator_confirmed_at_san_diego_comic_con_last_july_that_no_less_than_17_dragons_would_appear_on_screen_if_we_ve_already_seen_syrax_and_caraxes_others_are_going_to_show_up_during_the_first_and_second_season_of_the_show_since_it_has_already_been_ordered_by_hbo">If Daenerys had three dragons in Game of Thrones, the number of creatures present in House of The Dragon is going to be huge. Ryan J. Condal, the TV show co-creator, confirmed at San Diego Comic Con last July that no less than 17 dragons would appear on screen. If we’ve already seen Syrax and Caraxes, others are going to show up during the first and second season of the show, since it has already been ordered by HBO.</string>
    <string name="still_during_the_2022_san_diego_comic_con_george_r_r_martin_who_is_very_invested_in_house_of_the_dragon_revealed_that_the_show_was_inspired_from_an_english_civil_war_of_succession_like_game_of_thrones_which_was_loosely_based_on_the_war_of_the_roses_i_get_inspiration_from_history_and_then_i_take_elements_from_history_and_i_turn_it_up_to_11_he_said_house_of_the_dragon_is_based_on_an_earlier_period_in_history_called_the_anarchy_henry_i_the_king_of_england_his_only_legitimate_son_drowned_while_trying_to_cross_the_english_channel_that_left_him_with_only_one_legitimate_child_his_daughter_matilda_he_named_her_his_heir_and_made_all_the_lords_of_the_kingdom_swear_an_oath_to_her_and_when_he_died_most_of_the_lords_of_the_kingdom_forgot_about_that_oath_or_said_no_it_doesn_t_apply_her_cousin_stephen_then_crosses_the_channel_and_takes_control_it_begins_this_period_the_anarchy_where_matilda_and_stephen_fought_that_was_the_inspiration">Still during the 2022 San Diego Comic Con, George R. R. Martin, who is very invested in House of The Dragon revealed that the show was inspired from an English civil war of succession. “Like Game of Thrones, which was loosely based on the War of the Roses. I get inspiration from history, and then I take elements from history, and I turn it up to 11”, he said. “[\'House of the Dragon\'] is based on an earlier period in history called the Anarchy. Henry I, the King of England, his only legitimate son drowned while trying to cross the English channel. That left him with only one legitimate child, his daughter Matilda. He named her his heir and made all the Lords of the Kingdom swear an oath to her. And when he died, most of the lords of the kingdom forgot about that oath or said, ‘No, it doesn’t apply’. Her cousin, Stephen, then crosses the channel and takes control. It begins this period, The Anarchy, where Matilda and Stephen fought. That was the inspiration.”</string>
    <string name="HOTD_info1">According to Variety, every episode of the first season of House of the Dragon cost approximately 20 million dollars. That’s 200 million dollars for this first chapter of ten episodes. In comparison, Game of Thrones episodes cost 6 million dollars for the first seasons et 15 millions for the last ones.</string>
    <string name="dots">...............................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................</string>
</resources>